<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on All of Time and Space</title>
    <link>http://all-of-time-and-space.de/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on All of Time and Space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 02:06:34 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://all-of-time-and-space.de/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hoch Hinaus Und Tief Hinab</title>
      <link>http://all-of-time-and-space.de/posts/hoch-hinaus-und-tief-hinab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 02:06:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://all-of-time-and-space.de/posts/hoch-hinaus-und-tief-hinab/</guid>
      <description>So, da sind wir wieder!
Nach unserem Besuch in Upnor Castle ging es Richtung Nottingham, durch den malerischen Sherwood Forest, Heimstätte von Robin Hood und seinen Getreuen. Eine Nacht zuvor nächtigten wir hoch oben auf dem Ivinghoe Beacon, 233 Meter über dem Meeresspiegel mit fantastischer Aussicht über die umliegenden Lowlands. Nach ein wenig Fresh-Air-Snapping und Bergwandern fanden wir uns in Nottingham wieder…
Oder besser gesagt darunter! Unter der Stadt nämlich, mit hartem Schweiß mit dem Zweispitz in den Sandstein getrieben, erstrecken sich meilenweite Tunnelsysteme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arriving in England</title>
      <link>http://all-of-time-and-space.de/posts/arriving-in-england/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 22:33:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://all-of-time-and-space.de/posts/arriving-in-england/</guid>
      <description>We made it!  We had three days of preparation, hours of planning and discussions and one day of relaxing by the river before we drove to Calais.
There was a lot of different information flying around. Some websites said you can only cross the border to France if you have a negative Covid test that is less than 72 hours old, there was some hassle before we finally worked out if we had to self isolate in the UK, since we had to go through France (the answer being no, but only as long as we didn&amp;rsquo;t stop in France and leave our car) and the Covid-form we had to fill out before entering the UK wanted addresses of our stay, which of course we don&amp;rsquo;t really have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heidelberg</title>
      <link>http://all-of-time-and-space.de/posts/heidelberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 21:42:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://all-of-time-and-space.de/posts/heidelberg/</guid>
      <description>It’s been a while since we last posted anything. For the most part that is because we haven’t really been doing anything super exciting.
We visited Frankfurt for a day, where we got some super cool sleeping bags from my godfather (thank you, again!!!) and then spent a couple of days by another lake where we spent most of our time just swimming and relaxing.
And now we are in Heidelberg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Besuch in der Vergangenheit</title>
      <link>http://all-of-time-and-space.de/posts/besuch-in-der-vergangenheit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 12:16:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://all-of-time-and-space.de/posts/besuch-in-der-vergangenheit/</guid>
      <description>Grüße an alle Freunde, die des Englischen nicht mächtig sind! Exklusiv und nur für euch gibts jetzt den ersten Eintrag KOMPLETT AUF DEUTSCH vom manischen Michi. Das bin ich!
Wir waren heute auf kurzem Familienbesuch in der Nähe von Wertheim und haben uns natürlich nicht die Gelegenheit entgehen lassen die fabelhafte Altstadt und Burganlage zu begutachten.
Die Burg Wertheim, erstmals erbaut im 12. Jhd. und bis zum dreißigjährigen Krieg erweitert, war Sitz des Adelsgeschlechts der Grafen von Wertheim und Mittelpunkt der Region mit gutem Ausblick auf die Umgebung.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the road again</title>
      <link>http://all-of-time-and-space.de/posts/on-the-road-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 13:27:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://all-of-time-and-space.de/posts/on-the-road-again/</guid>
      <description>We are back!
Mike spent two days cutting a hole in the bathroom, fixing the pipes and then carefully replacing the hole. Apparently the pipes are not entirely secure yet, but if all goes well that will be remedied tonight when we are in Nürnberg.
We also used the chance to clean our awning, reorganize and sort out some of our clothes and other things that we realized we don’t actually need and, of course, cuddled the cat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Jolly Good Fellow</title>
      <link>http://all-of-time-and-space.de/posts/a-jolly-good-fellow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 22:44:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://all-of-time-and-space.de/posts/a-jolly-good-fellow/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday was Mike’s birthday. Can you believe it, he is actually old now. Since I am seven months younger I take great joy in reminding him of that fact. Every year. See why our relationship works so well?
The day started out only semi-good. The spot we had chosen to camp at the previous night (near Neumarkt i.d. Opf) turned out to be right by a large traffic road and a building site, which meant we were woken loudly when the rest of the world decided they wanted to do nothing more than get to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>...Go!</title>
      <link>http://all-of-time-and-space.de/posts/go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 21:08:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://all-of-time-and-space.de/posts/go/</guid>
      <description>Ladies, Gents and people Non-gender,
after weeks of renovating, repairing, sewing and throwing out things just for the heck of it, we are now officially off!
Well…. When I say we‘re off, we left last night (at 5 minutes to Midnight, just because I like the name of the song) and managed - drumroll - three kilometers! And what an adventure that was: Up steep hills and down scary valleys (well… one of each), right up to a thousand year old oak tree, where we set up camp for the night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready, Steady...</title>
      <link>http://all-of-time-and-space.de/posts/ready-steady/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 17:27:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://all-of-time-and-space.de/posts/ready-steady/</guid>
      <description>Lilo and Mike were originally due to leave in May, but their journey had to be postponed because of the pandemic. Now they are finally ready to set off on their adventures, and their friends want to wish them all the best&amp;hellip;
Dear Lilo and Mike, Roads go ever ever on,  Over rock and under tree,  By caves where never sun has shone,  By streams that never find the sea;  Over snow by winter sown,  And through the merry flowers of June,  Over grass and over stone,  And under mountains in the moon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>